British Columbia Honey Producers Association fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Subject files, 1936 - 2000; F-147-8; 32 cm of textual records 3 photographs
  Files were arranged by the archivist.
  Textual records; Photographic materials
  - BC Department of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1975; F-147-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
  - BC Ministry of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1976; F-147-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
  - BC Ministry of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1977; F-147-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
  - BC Ministry of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1978; F-147-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
  - BC Ministry of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1979; F-147-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
  - BC Ministry of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1980; F-147-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - BC Ministry of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1983; F-147-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - BC Ministry of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - annual report, 1985; F-147-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Bear damage to apiaries, 1971; F-147-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Beekeeping courses (notes and lectures on beekeeping, etc.), 1953 - 1958; F-147-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Boone / Hodgson / Wilkinson Trust fund, 1973 - 1979; F-147-8-0-0-11; Files pertaining to the BHW Trust Fund are also found in the Boone Hodgson Wilkinson Trust Fund Records sub-series (F-147-1-8). (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Honey promotion, 1976 - 1977; F-147-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Information bureau (BCHPA), F-147-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Meetings / programs, 1963 - 1965; F-147-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Membership lists, office bearers - general divisions (BCHPA), 1963 - 1967; F-147-8-0-0-15; Files pertaining to membership are also found in the Membership Records sub-series (F-147-1-7). (Archival box - standard 147-16)
  - Membership lists - Capital Region division (BCHPA), 1973; F-147-8-0-0-16; Files pertaining to membership are also found in the Membership Records sub-series (F-147-1-7). (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - Newsletters (various), 1968 - 1977; F-147-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - Office bearers (BCHPA), 1936 - 1975; F-147-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - Peace River history, 1966 - 1970; F-147-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
    Textual records; Peace River
  - Honeybee stock improvement, 1979 - 1983; F-147-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - Honeybee stock improvement, 1981; F-147-8-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - Honeybee stock improvement, 1981 - 1983; F-147-8-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - Three photographs, 1958; F-147-8-0-0-23; 3 photographs (Archival box - standard 147-17)
    File consists of three black and white photographs. Personalities pictured include Harvey Boone, John Stann, Lew Truscott, Ed Shinkle, George Reed, George Wilkinson, Professor Harris, Professor Townsend, John Corner and Mr. Conner.
    Photographic materials
  - BC Department of Agriculture, Apiculture branch - outward correspondence, 1962 - 1967; F-147-8-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - BC Federation of Agriculture - miscellaneous, 1969 - 1971; F-147-8-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 147-17)
  - BC Honey Producers' history - contributions to manuscript, 1994 - 1995; F-147-8-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
  - B.C.H.P.A. Educational Library collection list, 2000; F-147-8-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
- Other Associations and Divisions records, 1941 - 1998; F-147-9; 18 cm of textual records
  Series comprises records made or received by the Association's Divisions and other associations considering affiliation with the BCHPA. Records include correspondence, minutes, newsletters, and other documents.
  Files F-147-9-0-0-1 through F-147-9-0-0-24 are arranged alphabetically. Files F-147-9-0-0-25 through F-147-9-0-0-32 are arranged chronologically.
  - BCHPA Abbotsford Division, 1978 - 1984; F-147-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - Canadian Honeybee Research Association, 1983; F-147-9-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Central Cariboo Division, 1981 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Comox Valley Division, 1978 - 1984; F-147-9-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Cowichan Beekeepers Association, 1982 - 1984; F-147-9-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Kamloops Division, 1979 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Maple Ridge Division, 1978 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Nanaimo Division, 1978 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA North Okanagan Division, 1979 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA North Peace Division, 1978 - 1982; F-147-9-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Okanagan Pollination Division, 1980 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Pemberton Division, 1979 - 1982; F-147-9-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Port Alberni Division, 1979 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Powell River Division, 1979 - 1984; F-147-9-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Prince George Division, 1978 - 1981; F-147-9-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Quesnel Division, 1978 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - Richmond Beekeepers' Association, 1980 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Shuswap Division, 1981 - 1982; F-147-9-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA South Fraser Division, 1978 - 1984; F-147-9-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA South Okanagan Division, 1979 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA South Peace Division, 1981 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Squamish Division, 1979 - 1982; F-147-9-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA Terrace Division, 1979 - 1983; F-147-9-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - BCHPA West Kootenays Division, 1979 - 1984; F-147-9-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 147-18)
  - Minute book: South Okanagan Division BCHP Association, 1941 - 1961; F-147-9-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - South Okanagan Division BC Honey Producers' Association - record of financial transactions, 1941 - 1962; F-147-9-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - Okanagan Valley Pollination Association, [ca. 1964 - 1989]; F-147-9-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - Super News - BCHPA South Okanagan Division newsletters, 1985 - 1987; F-147-9-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - South Fraser Division B.C.H.P.A. newsletters, 1985 - 1993; F-147-9-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - British Columbia Honey Producers Association North Okanagan (Vernon) Division - news for members (one page copy), 1988; F-147-9-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - Central Cariboo Beekeepers Association - news for members (one page copy), 1991; F-147-9-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - Beewise: newsletter of the Comox Valley Beekeepers Association (single issue), 1998; F-147-9-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 147-25)